TOFIQUE ASIF ALI BARUDGAR



With an experience of over 4 years across diverse projects, I am an architect designer who is capable of working independently to deadlines and enjoys working in a proactive manner within fast moving and challenging environment in the commercial world with a keen interest in new trends and developments in Architectural design.

PERSONAL

Name:

Tofique Asif Ali Barudgar

DOB:

26th May 1989

Marital Status:

Married

Nationality:

Indian

Languages:

English, Hindi, Marathi

CONTACT

Mobile:

+91 7276836470 / 9372307163

Email: barudgartofique@yahoo.in

Skype ID: live:barudgartofique

Address:

88, Haji Nizammudin Bldg, S.V Road Old Khar (West), Mumbai-400052.

OBJECTIVE

To seek a position in an organization that will offer me professional growth and opportunity to utilize and enhance my technical and analytical skills.

KEYSKILLS & RESPONSIBILITIES

- Conceptualize design
- Research and Sustainability
- Deliver project integration
- Co-ordination and Execution in different phases of project.
- Preparing GFC drawings.

EDUCATION

- **B. Arch** | 2014-MGM'S Jawaharlal Nehru Engineering College, Aurangabad, MS-India.
- Completed BIM-Architecture from XSCAD, Mumbai.
- Certified Building Information Modelling professional.

SOFTWARE PROFICIENCIES

- Revit Architecture
- Navisworks
- AutoCAD
- Sketch-Up
- Photoshop
- Gantt Project
- MS Office
- Fusion 360

KEY PROJECTS

- Residential Interiors | 250 sqm | For GA Design consultants LLP | **Deonar Mumbai.**
- SOHO-Small Offices and Housing | 26,000 Sqm | For GA Design Consultants LLP **Panchshil**, **Pune**.
- Research on Hydoponic System | For GA Design consultants LLP |
 Panchshil, Pune.
- Housing Project | 40 acre | For GA Design consultants LLP |
- Panchshil, Pune.
- Hotel Baliraja |3 acre | Harshraj Mane and Associates | **Beed, Maharashtra.**
- Residential Interior | 170 sqm | For Harshraj Mane and Associates | Sewri, Mumbai.
- Corporate Interior | 400 sqm | For Harshraj Mane and Associates | Feedback Infra, Mumbai.
- Community Masjid | 1150sqm | For Khalid and Associates | **Rajasthan**.

TOFIQUE ASIF ALI BARUDGAR

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

GA Design	consultant LLP
	Architect

Chembur, Mumbai - India

April 2018 to April 2019

GA is at the forefront of sustainable and responsible design, Using cutting edge technology like BIM, Virtual Reality and 3D printing. Ga communicates with client at a different dimensions with Architecture, Interiors and lighting under one roof, GA follows as integrated and cohesive design philosophy, delivering holistic design

solution. Ga services its client globally.

As an Architect with limited experience but with good basics, My role was to co-ordinate directly with principal Architect creating concept and design mentored by him and turned into more workable and practical.

- SOHO-Small Offices and Housing, Pune | 26,000 sqm
- Warje Housing project.Pune | 40 Acre
- Residential Interior for Mr.Ganti, Deonar, Mumbai | 250 sqm
- Research and Development on hydroponics soiless planting system
- Working on Revit since April 2018

Harshraj Mane and Associates

Architect

Nov 2015 to Mar 2018

Sion, Mumbai - India

A small designed based firm with a lead architect and a small team dealt Small to medium size project. My role and responsibilities here, being a small firm involved every thing from designing, detailing, model making, site visits, meetings and co-ordination, here I have gained a good understanding of detailing.

- Hotel at beed
- Kishore pumps, Pune
- Residential Apartment, Titwala
- Residential Interiors, Sewri
- Feedback Infra corporate office, Andheri
- Maximus Events office, Andheri.
- Polo Club-In Kitchen, Mahalaxmi
- Number of Bungalows, Interiors and Presentation drawings.

Khalid and Associates

Architect

My first job, a very small design firm Team dealt with small to medium size projects, My roles and responsibilities here, being a small firm involves everything from designing, detailing, presentation drawings, Co-ordination and site visits.

Aug 2014 to Aug 2015

Santacruz, Mumbai - India

- Khatri House, Rajasthan
- Masjid, Rajasthan
- Worked on presentation and working drawings.

Academics

• Completed Thesis Dissertation on **Desert Resort**, Rajasthan.